"Sorry, your party is dead..."
Eyes of a Stranger is a horror, thriller film directed by Ken Wiederhorn.
A TV newswoman catches a pervert watching her
sister who cannot see, hear or speak.
Jane Harris, played by Lauren Tewes.
Tracy Harris, played by Jennifer Jason Leigh.
Stanley Herbert, played by John DiSanti.
David, played by Peter DuPre.
Debbie Ormsley, played by Gwen Lewis.
Dr. Bob, played by Robert Small.
Eyes of a Stranger is a 1981 American slasher film directed by Ken
Wiederhorn, and starring Lauren Tewes and Jennifer Jason Leigh.
The plot concerns a newscaster in Miami who suspects that her
neighbor may be a local rapist and serial killer.
It features makeup effects by Tom Savini.
The film explores themes of miami, florida, sister,
serial killer, reporter, slasher.
The tone is dark and intense.